[{"answer": "Well, I've got to get some water.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "How are you, sir?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Well, let's start with taxes for a moment.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Twelve million was his last --", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "And when Romney says he's going to create, well how many million jobs?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "You're not the only country that' broken the rule like that.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "How can we give to foreign aide?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, you're certainly not as broke as many countries around the world.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "How in debt are we?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Sure we can have involvement if they ask us.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "You don't think Americans have any involvement in any country in the world?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, the argument would be to prevent another war in that nation.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Why are we still there?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Because our military today --", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Isn't that a reality?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Sure, we'd be safe.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Would America be safer?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "I'm not saying necessarily to get rid of embassies.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Without any embassies in any country?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Yes, but that wasn't true about the Second World War, was it?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "The reality is sometimes you have to oppress a bad guy, don't you?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "At war all the time?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, because --", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Why should he get another four years?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Well, first, Governor, how are you doing?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "It'll require you the people to do it for me.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Governor, my question is, if you were to run as independent, completely unaffiliated from any political party whatsoever, do you feel that that would help or hinder your ability to ultimately gain valid access in all 50 states?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "And the only way that will help, two criteria must happen.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "-- put your butt on the line?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "But Jesse, will you be running or not, in 2016?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I don't have a problem with it.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "My question to you is, as a former Navy SEAL, do you agree or disagree with the recent released book by the six-member SEAL Team and -- and the objections of the Pentagon?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, he's out now.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "They all sign up, don't they, to not write about their experiences?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "What we're all agreed on is that the death of Osama bin Laden was a good thing.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "If he doesn't put in jeopardy anyone, why -- why is our government so up in arms about that he does this?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No, because I think a lot of times these uprisings are orchestrated, I believe.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Or from all we're seeing now in the Middle East, all the uprisings, all the kind of reverse Arab Spring, if you like, are you concerned that it may be a hornet nest getting out of control?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "In Libya, in Egypt.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Backing in what?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "We're here wanting to give democracy to people who lived, in my opinion, in the stone age.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "And are we now perhaps seeing the results of not knowing too well who they are?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Could be.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "They're all about religion and oil and corporations?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I'm not being naive, sir.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "You're being slightly naive, aren't you?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Because the people who did it were identified and we knew who they were.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "How did they know who did this so quickly like they did Lee Harvey Oswald, how quick they knew Lee Harvey Oswald killed Kennedy?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "A lot, actually.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "How much studying have you actually done of 9/11 other than what the government's told you and what mainstream media has told you?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I know a lot about it.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Because --", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Then why hasn't anyone been brought up for trial?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, first, let me state that Iran has to do this.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "If you were the American presidents, with all the jungle drums beating now about Iran, would you take any military action?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "None.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "How many political offices have you held?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Hello, governor?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well, politics in America, the problem -- the major problem is the Democrats and Republicans, as I explained in my book, \"Democrips and Rebloodicans, No More Games in Government,\" they've created a system based completely on bribery.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "And how do you think we can fix that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Well, the best thing I can tell you, Piers, is this: Mexico has strict gun control.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Why it is that Americans -- to me, it seems, so many Americans can not divorce their right to defend themselves with a gun to the apparent right to go and buy 6,000 rounds of ammunition, high powered assault weapons, and go and murder Americans?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "ENTURA: No, not at all.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "It's inarguable, isn't it?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "It's a facile argument.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Do we go to the Ford Motor Company and tell them, stop making these automobiles because people get drunk and kill people in cars?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "It's a facile.", "docId": "120917pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "It's a what?", "qSentId": 647}]